<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidQuiz</string>
    <string name="text_start">START</string>
    <string name="text_home">Home</string>
    <string name="text_result_analysis">RESULT ANALYSIS</string>
    <string name="text_play_again">PLAY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="text_congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="text_next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="hint_question">Question</string>
    <string name="hint_option_a">Option A</string>
    <string name="text_option_b">Option B</string>
    <string name="text_option_c">Option C</string>
    <string name="text_option_d">Option D</string>
    <string name="text_loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="text_empty_database">There isn\'t data yet!</string>
    <string name="hint_score">Score: 5/10</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz App</string>
    <string name="result_1">
        1. Which are the modules of Web layer?
        Correct answer - A) WebSocket, Servlet, Web, Portlet
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_2">
        2. Which is the correct implementation class of BeanFactory?
        Correct answer - A) XmlBeanFactory
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_3">
        3.What is true about list collection configuration elements?
        Correct answer - A)  This helps in wiring a list of values, allowing duplicates.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_4">
        4. What is bean autowiring?
        Correct answer - A)  Autowiring lets Spring resolve collaborators (other beans) for your bean by inspecting the contents of the BeanFactory without using constructor-arg and property elements.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_5">
        5. What is RequestHandledEvent:event?
        Correct answer - C)  This event is published when the HTTP session is initialized or refreshed.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_6">
        6. How around advice works?
        Correct answer - A) Run advice before and after the advised method is invoked.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_7">
        7. Which of the following database is not supported using jdbcTemplate?
        Correct answer - C) NoSql
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_8">
        8.  Expression Language/ SpEL was introduced in which version of spring framework.
        Correct answer - C) 3.0
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_9">
        9. Which of the following class can be used to call Stored Procedures in spring?
        Correct answer - D) SimpleJdbcCall
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_10">
        10. What is the use of a content provider in Android?
        Correct answer - C) A content provider is used to share information between Android applications.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_11">
        11. While developing android application developers can test their apps on
        Correct answer - D) Apps can be tested in all the sources mentioned above.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_12">
        12. In android, mini activities are also known as
        Correct answer - C) In android, mini activities are also known as Fragments
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_13">
        13. Among the following choose the one which converts Java bytecode into Dalvik bytecode
        Correct answer - A)  dex compiler converts convert JAVA bytecode into Dalvik bytecode.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_14">
        14. The services in android can be stopped using which of the following method?
        Correct answer - B) stopSelf() and stopService() method can be used to stop services in android.
    </string>
    
    <string name="result_15">
        15. Activity in Android can be killed using?
        Correct answer - D) Activity in Android can be killed using both finishActivity (int requestCode) and finish() method.
    </string>

</resources>
